<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on J Sims</title><link>https://jess-sims.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on J Sims</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 08:06:25 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jess-sims.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to create a Hugo Website</title><link>https://jess-sims.github.io/posts/hugo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://jess-sims.github.io/posts/hugo/</guid><description>Hugo is a fast, open-source static website generator with many contributors and themes available to suit various needs. It&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic resource for blogs, portfolios and documentation sites and a great tool to keep web hosting costs low as Hugo sites may be hosted on github pages, netlifier and other similar services. As there are various themes available it is also relatively simple to configure a website with minimal coding and command line experience.</description></item><item><title>Git and GitHub</title><link>https://jess-sims.github.io/posts/git/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 11:23:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://jess-sims.github.io/posts/git/</guid><description>Git is an extremely useful distributed version control system which allows the user to track changes to their files. Git is frequently used among developers, technical writers and other collaborative professions to manage their projects and releases.
GitHub is a hosting service which works hand in hand with Git so that collaborators may share their projects by hosting the main and current copy of the project on a GitHub repository. From GitHub, users may pull a copy of the project to their local machine, open problem reports and create branches and merge requests which may then be reviewed by the project owner(s).</description></item><item><title>Using Markdown</title><link>https://jess-sims.github.io/posts/markdown/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:56:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://jess-sims.github.io/posts/markdown/</guid><description>Markdown is a lightweight markup language used to make webpages easier on on the eye when displayed and simplier to read in plain text format. Markdown is widely popular due to its ease of use and its acceptance by many applications such as documentation systems, note-taking applications and messaging systems.
The below examples showcase some of the basic Markdown syntax elements, however, there are more features and Markdown flavours available depending on the Markdown implementation or specific application you&amp;rsquo;re using.</description></item></channel></rss>